Jamie Leviner

Software Engineer Born 1980 in Florence, SC



About me

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

Skills

JavaScript jQuery VueJS

CSS/LESS/SASS

C#/ASP.NET MVC Go

Intercom PostgreSQL

Contact



✓ levinerjamie@gmail.com

(843) 229-1193

) jamieleviner.com

jamieleviner

Experience

Software Engineer

ACS Technologies
July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Software Engineer-Associate

ACS Technologies July 2016 - July 2017 Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Software Development Apprentice

ACS Technologies
August 2015 - July 2016
Making coffee and baking cookies.

Intern

ACS Technologies May 2015 - August 2016

Education

Francis Marion University

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics

Jan 2011 - Dec 2014

Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

Projects

best-resume-ever

Vue

jamieleviner.com

e Jekyll My personal website. Created using the

Build fast and easy multiple beautiful resumes and create your best cv ever! Made with Vue and LESS.

My personal websi jekyll theme Jalpc.